

ARUN MOHAN SETA

Flutter Team Lead

I am Arun Flutter Developer at AppStoneLab Technologies LLP, as an independent and self-motivated graduate with more than 5 years of experience in the mobile development industry, Involved in product testing, management, and rollout of apps in Appstore. I started my journey as a fresher mobile developer and as time went on I got a chance to lead the team which helped me to grow my knowledge and my teammates as well.

arunseta432@gmail.com



+17056181762



Sudbury, Ontario, Canada

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Flutter Developer AppStoneLab Technologies LLP

11/2019 - Present Responsibilities

Surat, Gujarat, India.

- Provide insight to the team as to the best mobile application development practices and techniques.
- Leads and directs the workforce in problem identification, problem-solving, and implementing continuous improvement measures.
- Deliver Projects with High Quality and High Performance.
- Ability to understand business requirements and translate them into technical requirements.
- Understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git.
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use.
- Experience with self-testing to minimize and fix issues, strong problem solving/debugging skills.
- Experience with Objective-C, Swift, Dart, Java, Flutter, Javascript, and C/C++ Programming.

Senior iOS Developer AppStoneLab Technologies LLP

12/2017 - 11/2019

Surat, Gujarat, India.

Responsibilities

- Gathering the project requirements.
- Client communication.
- Build user interfaces designed by UI/UX designers.
- Complete end-to-end development of the project within specified time.
- Uploading the application to AppStore.

Fresher iOS Developer AppStoneLab Technologies LLP

01/2015 - 12/2017

Surat, Gujarat, India.

Responsibilities

- Learn Swift Language, UI Kit and Core Data basics.
- Designing and building mobile applications for the iOS platform.
- Identifying potential problems and resolving application bottlenecks.
- Maintaining the code and atomisation of the application.
- Deploy iOS Applications to the App Store and create maintainable code.
- Collaborate with third-party support and service to clients to ensure that the application stays operational.

SKILLS

MVC/MVVM code Pattern

Software-App Testing

Apply industry standards during the software development process to ensure high quality of code

Ability to assimilate new technologies quickly

PROJECTS WORKED ON

GSEB Shiksha (Educational)

App will provide you with important learning material like books & videos on your mobile which will help you keep learning.

Gujarati calendar (Religious)

App serves panchang results with planetary calculations. It is an informative app for people who speak Gujarati across the globe.

Nube TV (iOS & TvOS) (Entertainment)

 A platform designed to meet the needs of local internet operators in Spain, app. provides a quality system combined with a large selection of channels, content on-demand, and customer service.

Kanga (Training/Exercise)

Kanga is Training and Exercise base app to record different reading to use for physiotherapy.

POPPI VIP (VIP table booking and chatting)

 POPPI is a members-only platform for VIP event invitations in USA such as bottle service, cabanas, concerts, boat parties, and more.

The Build (Construction)

Construction app for the jobsite. connects entire field team, from the project manager all the way down to each specialty contractor's foreman, on one construction management platform.

SGA Watches (E-commerce)

The WatchXchange is a member - only virtual marketplace where one will be able to view all the products up for sale, they can also search for watches they are looking for, and converse with other members using our group chat function.

Catch (Dating)

The top free dating app, making it the place to meet new people based on location checking and chatting.

Concierge Pharmacy (Pharmacy)

Access a history of your medications and Rx numbers. Set reminders when to refill your medications. Set reminders when to take your medications.

GoodRep (Social)

Write stories about the person you admire, get comments and likes on stories, make new connections by following other users. something like saying thanks in different way to your friend.

CERTIFICATION COURSE

Basics of computer programing Online C, C++, Swift free course.

08/2014 - 12/2014,

Surat, Gujarat, India.

HONOR AWARDS

Hive Five

Appstonelab Technologies.

 Awarded due to excellent performance and strong team co-ordination and team work with best skill to lead the team.

Sports Certificate

Shree Swaminarayan Gurukul English medium school, Ved Road, Surat, Gujarat, India.

 Awarded on different sports games at school level like Volleyball, Kho-Kho, High jump, Long jump, Tug of war.

Academic Certificate

Shree Swaminarayan Gurukul English medium school, Ved Road, Surat, Gujarat, India.

 Awarded to perform excellent and top position in secondary education.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

GymTown

 Beautiful life is about a perfect balance of healthy body, mind and soul. But in today's rat race of success, balance is disturbed. The concept and inception of GYM TOWN is motivated to bring the balance back through systematic and customised approach towards fitness through the means of exercise and physiotherapy solutions.

PantryOn

 PantryOn is a useful, no-nonsense app built to simplify your grocery shopping process, minimize time spent grocery shopping, and maximize time spent doing something you truly enjoy.

Renting App

 List properties available for rent, be it your apartment, independent house, a residential plot or a farmhouse, camera and many more.

EDUCATION

Primary-Secondary schooling education Shree Swaminarayan Gurukul English medium school, Ved Road, Surat, Gujarat, India.

06/1998 - 04/2010,

Surat, Gujarat, India.

Bachelor of Engineering

Sitarambhai Naranjibhai Patel Institute Of Technology & Research centre. (Baben-Bardoli) (Formerly known as Vidhyabharti Trust Institute of Technology & Research Centre.)

06/2010 - 04/2014,

Bardoli, Gujrat, India

MSc Computational Science

Laurentian University (French: Université Laurentienne), Officially the Laurentian University of Sudbury.

935 Ramsey Lake Rd, Sudbury, ON P3E 2C6

09/2022 - 09/2024,

Sudbury, Ontario, Canada.

(Expected to be graduated in 2023 September.)